<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2016-12-27T14:54:38-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">Bryan Rolando’s blog</title><subtitle>roli's blog about programming, software development, and technology.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">hello world!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hello-world!.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="hello world!" /><published>2016-12-14T16:05:03-06:00</published><updated>2016-12-14T16:05:03-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hello-world!</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hello-world!.html">&lt;p&gt;One of the things I enjoy the most is learning, just by the fact that gathering knowledge might be useful in the present and future is appealing enough to spend (invest) time on it.
There’s a lot of ways to learn: by observing others, by summarizing, reading, hearing, by making, and teaching (among others.) In my experience those last two are the most efficient ways to learn and make the facts stick to your brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why I thought it would be a nice idea to have a place, this blog, where I can write interesting articles about software development, reinforcing and sharing knowledge along the way. Then it will be easier to refer back to concepts I tend to forget, look back at the way I used to code and think in a few years from now, and possibly make some of this content useful for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully by doing this I can actually get better at writing. I’m not particularly bad, but I don’t like to “over decorate” my phrases. I’ve also found that I tend to write very concisely, which from a programming standpoint could be a godsend (since clarity is often achieved through brevity).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Hacking!&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">One of the things I enjoy the most is learning, just by the fact that gathering knowledge might be useful in the present and future is appealing enough to spend (invest) time on it.
There’s a lot of ways to learn: by observing others, by summarizing, reading, hearing, by making, and teaching (among others.) In my experience those last two are the most efficient ways to learn and make the facts stick to your brain.</summary></entry></feed>
